她们回来了
There they are.
你们俩早上有按时把车还回去吗
Did you girls get the car back in time this morning?
有  时间刚刚好  多亏了卡洛琳
Yep, just in time, thanks to Caroline.
她完全无视限速的标志
She was ignoring speed limit signs
就像她无视流浪汉一样
like she does homeless people.
有个州警用四个字形容我开车
A state trooper called my driving
"刑事过失"
criminally negligent.
我真为你骄傲
I was so proud.
当时差点都要感动落泪了
I might've even gotten emotional,
但我必须巧舌如簧求警察别开罚单
but I had to talk our way out of the ticket,
还得在脱衣色诱时保持专业  所以没哭
and I like to be professional when my shirt's off.
你们没被开罚单吗
You didn't get a ticket?
昨天我就因为走进全食超市而被捕了
Yesterday, I got arrested for just walking into Whole Foods.